Guide to the Merle Hoffman Papers, circa 1944-2012 and undated, bulk 1961-2000 RL.00557
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2012-0049), dated 1978-2012 and undated, 7 boxes
  - Gold, Dr. Martin, 1994, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Gold, Dr. Martin: Play, undated (Box 3)
  - Grant: Choices, Adelphi Research Program, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Greenberg, Mary Lou, 1991, 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Guttmacher Institute, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Hassibi, Dr. Mahin, 1995 (Box 3)
  - HIV/AIDS, undated (Box 3)
  - H. J. Rubenstein, 1979 (Box 3)
  - HMOs Business Office, undated (Box 3)
  - Hoffman, Aileen, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Hoffman, Merle CV, undated (Box 3)
  - Howard J. Rubenstein Associates, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Hunter, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Intimate Wars Promotional Material, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Jennings, James A., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Kagan, Julia, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Karlsson, Kent, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Katz, Melinda, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Lamar, Laura M., 2012 (Box 4)
  - Lardiere, Michael, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Lardiere, Michael: Project Liberty, 2001 (Box 4)
  - LeFrak Center Photos, 1998 (Box 4)
  - LeFrak/Federal Realty Ltd. Partnership, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Letterhead, undated (Box 4)
  - Loder, Asjylyn: MH Management, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Loder, Asjylyn: Research Assistant Notes, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Loder, Asjylyn: Exit Notes, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Logan, Tracy: BBC, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Lowy, Beverly, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Manager's Meetings, 35962 (Box 4)
  - Manager's Meetings, 1998-2003, 29 folders (Box 4)
  - Marc & W, 1994-1995, 2003-2004 (Box 4)
  - Marie Stopes International, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Marinoff, Lou, 2000, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Marketing, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Matthew, Donna, 1996-1999, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - Matriarch Project, Suzanne Fiol, 1996, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Medical Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Medical Students for Choice, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Meetings, 1997, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Mehta, Nina, 1994, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Meltzer, Leila, November 1996 - January 1997 (Box 5)
  - Memos from Merle Hoffman, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health, 2003-2005, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Choices, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health Center: Correspondence and Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health Center: Policies and Procedures Manual, undated (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Confidential, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Director's Meeting, undated (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Health Fees & Reports, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: General, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Job Descriptions, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Minutes, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health, Office of, 2000-2006 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health, Office of: Agreement between NYS Office of Mental Health & CHOICES, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Operating Certificate, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Plan of Correction, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Plan of Correction, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: State Inspection, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health: Weekly Report, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Merle's License Information, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Michael, Jeannine, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Millett, Kate, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Gabrielle, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Maria, 1996-1999 (Box 5)
  - National Abortion Federation Bytes (WordBytes): Archive Information, 2003 (Box 6)
  - National Abortion Federation Correspondence: Membership-Subscription, 2006 (Box 6)
  - National Abortion Federation: Field Guide, undated (Box 6)
  - National Coalition of Abortion Providers, 1996, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Nixon, Hargrave, Devans & Doyle, 1997 (Box 6)
  - N.O.W. - National Organization for Women, 2002 (Box 6)
  - N.O.W. - National Organization for Women: Court Ruling, 2000 (Box 6)
  - N.O.W. - National Organization for Women: Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1996 (Box 6)
  - New York State Department of Health: Certificate Application, 1997 (Box 6)
  - New York State Department of Health, 1997, 1999, 2000 (Box 6)
  - NYU Women's Archive Project, 1996 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Aileen Wuornos Screening, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Carolyn Handel, 1991, 1992, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Correspondence with Merle Hoffman, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Linda Gustein, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Media Kit, 1993 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Ronni Sandroff, 1993, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Sally Owen, 1995 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Stoltenberg, John, 1994 (Box 6)
  - On the Issues: Website, undated (Box 6)
  - Pension: IRS, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Pension: NY Life Insurance Co., 2002 (Box 6)
  - Personnel Policy Manual, 2007 (Box 6)
  - Pharmacy Application, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 6)
  - Pickard, Paul, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Pioneer Feminist Directory, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Plan of Correction, 2000 (Box 6)
  - POA (Power of Attorney), 2007 (Box 6)
  - Poules, Bella, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Press Release, undated (Box 6)
  - Price, Sherry, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Ronald D. Hariri & Associates, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Rosalia, Annette, 1997, 1998, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Rose, Karen, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Rosen, Bruce, 2003 (Box 6)
  - RU 48, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Russo, Susan, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Sasso, Frances, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Sasso, Frances: MH Management, 2002, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Sasso, Michael, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Scanlon, John, 1980, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Schumer, Charles, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Security Threats, 1999-2002 (Box 6)
  - Sessler, Bonnie, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Shapiro, Ella, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Site Survey, January 24 2000 (Box 6)
  - Silver, Joy, 1994-2002, 6 folders (Box 6)
  - Silver, Joy: HMO, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Anne Mollegen, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Ilan, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Space Requirements Program, 2009 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Adelglass, 2003 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Business Cards, 2003 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Cardiology, 2001 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Meridian, 2002 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Pain Management, 2002 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Phixative, 2003 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Plastic Surgery, undated (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Printing, 2003 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Sleep Program, 2002 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Wallace, 2002 (Box 7)
  - StarCare: Web/Brochure Text, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Strategy, 2002 (Box 7)
  - SUMMONS, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Tax Deductions, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Transfer of Stock, 1987 (Box 7)
  - UNC/FCU, 2003, 2004 (Box 7)
  - UNC Follow Up, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Vacation - M. Hoffman, 1983, 1984, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Valady, Mohammed and Spielberger, John, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Veteran Feminist of America, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Veteran Feminist of America: E-mails, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Veteran Feminist of America: Events, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Veteran Feminist of America: Health Conference, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Veteran Feminist of America: Minutes, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Victim Services, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Who's Who, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Wirth, Ken, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Women's Review of Books, 2001, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Women's Review of Books: Mason, undated (Box 7)
  - Ziss Project, 2005, 2008 (Box 7)
  - Zweiman, Lora: MH Management, 2003 (Box 7)